(Mrs Latham:)Oh, I made you uncomfortable
last night.
(Mrs Latham:)I'm so sorry.
(Leonard:)No, that's okay.
(Mrs Latham:)No, it most
certainly is not.
(Mrs Latham:)Leonard, I'm making the
donation to your department
(Mrs Latham:)regardless of what
happens between us.
- Really?
- Well, of course.
(Mrs Latham:)There's no quid
pro quo here.
(Mrs Latham:)You and your colleagues are
doing remarkable research,
(Mrs Latham:)and you deserve the money.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Then what was
last night about?
I took a shot; sue me.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Mrs Latham:)You're a very
handsome man, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Mrs Latham:)It was foolish of me to
think someone your age
(Mrs Latham:)might ever be interested
in someone like me.
(Leonard:)Oh, don't say that.
(Leonard:)- You're a very attractive woman.
- Oh, please.
- No, it's true.
- Well, aren't you sweet.
(Mrs Latham:)Just for the record...
(Mrs Latham:)you'd remember a night with me
for the rest of your life.
(Leonard:)I'm sure I would.